Ashley Fuller

35 Clifford Avenue, Beeston, Nottingham, NG9 2PX, UK Email: ajfuller181193@gmail.com Mobile: 07519481108

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/ashley-fuller-169b86a5

Summary

I am an Electronics Engineer with two years' experience in planning and implementing software used for testing automotive radars. I am a highly motivated, organised individual who is well-practised in Python and Embedded C. I have experience with ARM-Cortex and NXP microcontrollers, as well as Xilinx and Altera FGPAs.

EXPERIENCE

ZF TRW Automotive Solihull, UK

Electronics Engineer

Oct 2017 - Present

- Writing Python and Embedded C software to perform hardware testing, using Git for version control.
- Using Vivado for Xilinx System-on-Chip Configuration.
- Working with different communication types: Ethernet(TCP/UDP), CAN protocols, SPI, I2C and UART.
- Mentoring new staff and training technicians to perform hardware testing.
- Testing and building hardware development equipment.
- Performing investigations and writing detailed reports of findings.

Nottingham Trent University

Nottingham, UK

Undergraduate Researcher

June 2016 - Sep 2016

- Working with microcontrollers and stepper motors to replicate the 'waggle dance' using a mechanical bee.
- Using Solidworks for system design, then CorelDRAW and a laser cutter to build parts for the project.
- Producing a written report and presenting the findings at a university conference.

Morrisons Nottingham, UK

Frozen Supervisor / Grocery Manager

Oct 2013 - Oct 2017

- Providing excellent customer service in both full and part-time roles.
- Communicating with and supervising colleges to manage a department.
- Meeting deadlines and exceeding regional sales targets for the department.

EDUCATION

Master of Science: Nottingham Trent University Grade: **Distinction**

Engineering (Electronics), 2017

- Dissertation title: Atrial Fibrillation Classification Using a Convolutional Neural Network (CNN).
- Designing and implementing a CNN in Python to analyse cardiac rhythm.
- Adapting the CNN for time series data, then training it using gradient descent to achieve 92% accuracy.
- Modules Taken: Embedded Systems, Wireless Communication, Software Engineering, Digital Control, Group Design Project, Research Methods and Major Project.

Bachelor of Science:

Nottingham Trent University

Grade: First Class

Physics with Astrophysics, 2016

- Dissertation title: Monitoring Light Pollution Instrumentation.
- Designing and implementing an automated light pollution surveying system using an Arduino.
- Presented at the National Astronomy Meeting 2016 and work acknowledged in 'Astronomy Now'.

Interests

I am a keen runner and enjoy church bell-ringing. I love to learn new skills in my spare time to expand my knowledge and passion for embedded systems, such as working through Udemy courses.

References

Available on Request